techsviewer.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy

[](https://techsviewer.com/ "Techsviewer") Offering Simple Solutions for Tech Problems

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Techsviewer collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.techsviewer.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The Techsviewer .

**Information We Automatically Collect**

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use the Services (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Services we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit. We will use such Usage Data to diagnose problems with our servers and software, to administer the Services, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party advertising networks and servers will also provide us reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked on the Services in a manner that does not identify personally any individual.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Affilate**

This site may contain Amazon

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/),  You can read Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Third Party Advertising**

[Third-party vendors and ad networks](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) are serving ads in this site. You can view the list of third party advertisers via the following links [AdWords third-party vendors ](https://support.google.com/3pascertification/table/4572577) & [Ad Exchange Vendors](https://support.google.com/3pascertification/table/4570113) You may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can  opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).   The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

**Google Analytics (Google)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data. Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – Opt Out

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
